Md. Juliush

Web Developer

Address: Keranigonj, Dhaka

Mobile: 01744341073

E-mail: ajuliush@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/ajuliush

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hi! My name is Md. Juliush. I am a web developer. I have been working as a professional software developer since 2021. I have also more skills on web design and development, software development using these tools such as HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, PHP (Laravel Framework), Rest API, apart from, Moreover, I am especially passionate on PHP, MySQL, JavaScript. I like to learn new things with the latest technology and learn about new people, chat and so on.

EXPERIENCE

Prediction LA. (Since October 2022 – November 2023)

- Design and develop several types of software like HR Management, Learning platform, websites & support clients.
- > Testing functionality for users and the backend.
- > Ensuring that integrations run smoothly.
- Assist other web developers of the organization to build other web applications and software for the organization
- > Daily work update in meeting with the
- Meeting with the client, collecting client requirements, analyzing software requirements, debugging, testing, and finally software delivery to the client.

Web Arts Factory. (Since January 2022 – October 2022)

- Design and develop several types of software like E-commerce, canteen management, education & Websites.
- ➤ Meeting with the client, collecting client requirements, analyzing software requirements, debugging, testing, and finally software delivery to the client.
- Assist other web developers of the organization to build other web applications and software for the organization.
- Daily work update in meeting with the team.



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- > Solid understanding of software development using **Laravel**.
- ➤ Solid understanding of OOP and model, view controller (MVC).
- > Problem-solving and critical mindset.
- > Experience working with **RESTful APIs**.
- Proficiency in HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery,AJAX, JSON, Bootstrap, and Rest API.
- Software Development using PHP and MySQL.
- ➤ Knowledge of database design and querying using **SQL**.
- > Desire and ability to Learn.
- Cloud Server Experience in AWS (Beginner)
- > Version Control Git & GitHub
- > Manage Post Man

PROJECTS

E-commerce Software

- > E-commerce Software for **Eurasia BD** cosmetics.
- > Technology: Laravel 8, Bootstrap, MySQL, jQuery, AJAX, JSON
- ➤ Url:https://savershall.com/suadmin

Canteen Management Software

- ➤ Canteen Management Software for **BRAC**.
- > Technology: Laravel 8, Bootstrap, MySQL, jQuery, AJAX, JSON.
- GitHub Link: https://github.com/ajuliush/canteen

HR Management

- > HR management for Prediction LA
- > Technology: Laravel 8, Bootstrap4, MySQL, jQuery, AJAX, JSON
- ➤ Url: https://hrmspla.predictionla.com/

COURSES & CERTIFICATES

➤ Completed a course on "Web Application Development with PHP and Frameworks" at "IsDB-BISEW" (August, 2019 – January, 2021).

EDUCATION

- > Bachelor of Business Admiration (BBA) at **Dhaka College**, **Dhaka**.
- ➤ Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC) at **Syed Azizul Haque Degree College.**

Reference

Parvej Ahmed

IT Business & Project Development Analyst Prediction Info Tech Baridhara DOHS, Dhaka

Mob: 01910-639273

E-mail: parvej.websoft@gmail.com

Md. Moshaidul Islam

Consultant IsDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Project Show & Tell Consulting Ltd. Mobile: 01714-111811

Email: moshaidul@showtellconsulting.com

Morshed Habib Sohel

Senior Trainer BhuiyanIt Limited Dhanmondi,Dhaka,Bangladesh

Mob: 01735-254295

E-mail: mhsohel017@gmail.com